pornhub4u.com 2014-07-02

# The Wizard Of Porn :: Notes on Security & Privacy

##  PRIVACY POLICY

This document contains important information on the use and disclosure of user information stored on The Wizard Of Porn

The security of your data is very important for The Wizard Of Porn and for this we apply the necessary measures to reduce the risk that they are lost or damaged.

This site expressly and strictly limits its enrollments or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age or over and who have attained at least the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet these criteria can not access or view the content of this Site do not know or are looking for information or personal data on persons who have not attained the age of majority.

**DATA COLLECTED**

  * Personal information:
  *     * Users are not registered, you can watch videos without registering and without any information being recorded or processed. However the visitor's IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information content.
    * Members: Registration is required for uploading videos, and use various other options. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration, such as date of birth, username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, marital status and sexual orientation may be added optionally after registration by the Members concerned to identify and make contact with other members that meet certain criteria. All of these data, with the exception of the email address and IP address information will become publicly accessible.
  * Uploaded content on the site or any personal information voluntarily disclosed online video content will become publicly available and may be recorded and used by others.
  * Cookies: When you visit The Wizard Of Porn, we send one or more cookies to your computer to uniquely identify the session of your browser. The Wizard Of Porn uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. Removing persistent cookies, some of the options of the site may not function properly.
  * Log File Information: When you visit The Wizard Of Porn, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the URL of reference, platform type, domain names, and the date and time of your request.
  * Email: If you contact us, we may keep records of correspondence

**USAGE**

  * Your personally identifiable information submitted to The Wizard Of Porn are used to provide the user with the options of the site and personalized options.
  * The chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other users with the loaded content, including videos, comments, and messages sent via the private email to The Wizard Of Porn. Other users can contact you through private messages.
  * All videos submitted to The Wizard Of Porn may be disseminated on the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or advertising without your consent.
  * We may use your email address without further consent for non-advertising, or administrative (such as communications of important changes to the site or customer support purposes.
  * We analyze aggregated user traffic information to optimize our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the experience of The Wizard Of Porn.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

  * If required to do so, The Wizard Of Porn may disclose information in compliance with legal obligations, pursuant to our Terms of Service and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of The Wizard Of Porn or Our members or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including political and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether it is not specified in the Terms of Service. It 'part of the policy of The Wizard Of Porn, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify any obligation to provide data to third parties.
  * Nel caso in cui vengano deliberatamente caricati materiali illegali, PormHub sarà tenuto a inoltrare tempestivamente tutte le informazioni disponibili alle autorità competenti senza alcun preavviso. \- Non condividiamo le informazioni personali disponibili (quali nome e indirizzo email) con altri, aziende terze a scopi commerciali o di marketing senza consenso o se non fanno parte di uno specifico programma o opzione che voi avrete la capacità di sottoscrivere o cancellare.

**SAFETY**

When we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which will allow you to access certain parts of our Site, you will be responsible for its confidentiality. We ask you not to share it with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission dell'informazioni via the Internet is not completely secure. The Wizard Of Porn uses the technical protection, management and physics in a reasonable manner for commercial purposes to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We can not, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to The Wizard Of Porn from you, what you made at your own risk

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to access and change your information directly on the website or by sending a request in the Contact Us section. If you have additional questions, please write to info [AT] thewizardofporn.com.
